Skateboard wheels on tracks are meh.
Another night just came and went.
Spamming hearts on brick brick walls, laughing loud duty calls.
Early morning, bus is late.
Teachers glaring for some shade.
Eyes have opened, shoes untied, still can't fit the dead inside.
I'm sick of all your stupid rules.
The way you act like we're all fools.
Suffer then life is killing me I just wanna break free Break free, break free Break free, break free Principal's office one more time Full on junk they call the crime Parents freaking out again while I'm hanging with my friends
They say I should grow up.
But their lives just went stuck.
Can't even take the lock and leave the town that makes me.
I'd stop all your stupid rules.
The way you act like we're all fools.
Suburban life is killing me.
I just wanna move out, but please don't move.
Break free!